afrugalfriend.net 2010-05-22

# Disclosures

This blog, http://www.afrugalfriend.net, is a personal blog written by me.

This blog contains links to other websites. While I try to link only to sites that share a high standard of privacy, I am not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices of other websites. All information that you submit on other websites is done so at your own risk. I do encourage you to read the privacy policy of each site that you provide personal information to.

This site links to various promotions (rebates, free samples, etc.) Please be aware that I do not personally guarantee the delivery/production of free samples or other deals promoted on this site. This site merely informs others about the free samples and links to various promotions. I do not provide the free samples or promotions.

This site is not intended for use by minors. This site does not knowingly solicit or market to minors.

I do not share, sell or lease any personal information that may be provided on this site.

This site may at times accept forms of cash advertising. This site may also accept various products, provided free of charge, to be looked at for possible review. Even though I may receive forms of compensation through review products, advertising and such, I always give my personal opinion about topics and/or products. While as of Jan 2010, this site has not written any “sponsored posts” for which we have been paid money, if this occurs in the future, that fact will be noted in the post itself.

I am an affiliate for various programs like commission junction and others. If sales occur (or leads or clicks as it may be), through a link from [http://www.afrugalfriend.net](http://www.afrugalfriend.net/), I may receive compensation. This may be in the form of a percentage commission or otherwise. Nonetheless, if I personally comment on any promotion, I will always state my personal and honest opinion.   Many of these promotions/deals would be discussed whether or not I received a form of compensation or not.

PRIVACY:

At http://www.afrugalfriend.net, the privacy of visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by http://www.afrugalfriend.net and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, http://www.afrugalfriend.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
http://www.afrugalfriend.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Commission Junction, and others, with more to likely be added in the future.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.afrugalfriend.net sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://www.afrugalfriend.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.afrugalfriend.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions, please feel free to contact me by email at afrugalfriend (at) hotmail (dot) com.
